[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular comedian and actor voiced the characters Ramon and Lovelace in the 2006 animated movie Happy Feet?", "correct_answer": "Robin Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Short", "Will Smith", "Steve Martin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the major purposes of Feng Shui is the search for the universal abstract energy or life force that governs our world. It is called this.", "correct_answer": "Chi", "incorrect_answers": ["Yi", "Ru Li", "Fu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the opera Mozart et Salieri?", "correct_answer": "Rimsky-Korsakov", "incorrect_answers": ["Berlioz", "Bizet", "Saint-Saiens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the Clydesdale horse introduced to North America?", "correct_answer": "1715", "incorrect_answers": ["1636", "1525", "1800"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you wish to surrender, you will do one of these white things.", "correct_answer": "You will raise a white flag.", "incorrect_answers": ["You will drive a white car.", "You will visit the White House.", "You will wear white underwear."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the most impressive feature of the Stegosaurus appearance, which makes it the most easily identifiable dinosaur even for the non-expert observer?", "correct_answer": "Kite-shaped plates", "incorrect_answers": ["Long neck", "Enormous tail", "Long curved horns"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Empire Strikes Back, Luke Skywalker finds out that Darth Vader is this relationship to him?", "correct_answer": "Father", "incorrect_answers": ["Uncle", "Brother", "Grandfather"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the movie The Break-Up, where do Gary and Brooke first meet?", "correct_answer": "At a baseball game", "incorrect_answers": ["At an art museum", "In Central Park", "At a basketball game"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Galveston, Indiana was the site of a deadly tornado in 1900.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1994 film Sleep With Me, Quentin Tarantino has a cameo in which he points out the homoerotic subtext of this 1986 action movie directed by Tony Scott.", "correct_answer": "Top Gun", "incorrect_answers": ["Cobra", "Beverly Hills Cop", "Lethal Weapon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these smoking devices operates by water-filtration and direct heat?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Hookah", "Water pipe", "Hubble-bubble"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The planet Neptune can be seen with the naked eye.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]